ENIOLA ADEBAYO

Greater London • (+44) 07485717472 • eniolaadebayo9@yahoo.com • LINKEDIN

PROFILE

I'm a 21-year-old student currently immersed in the world of English Language & Media Communications at university. During my studies, I found a thrilling new passion for technology, precisely Front-end Web Development, and I've since graduated from edX's Trilogy Bootcamp that specialises in that sector of Tech. This blend of linguistics and tech skills have given me a unique edge in problem-solving and analysis – an invaluable skill in this dynamic tech industry.

As I'm always hungry to learn, I'm constantly keeping up with the latest trends and technologies to enhance my abilities and stay in sync with this fast-paced field. I'm eager to connect with fellow professionals in tech and anyone who shares my fascination for language and communication.

I hope to explore new opportunities and ideas with you, as collaboration and growth are my driving forces.

EDUCATION

University of Essex

October 2020 – July 2024

English Language & Media Communications BA (Expecting 2:1 or higher)

Relevant coursework: Digital Society, Research Methods for Language & Linguistics

EdX *Trilogy Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Web Development*

November 2022 - March 2023

EdX June 2020 – August 2020

Exercising Leadership: Foundational Principles, Public Leadership

Frances Bardsley Academy for Girls

September 2013 – June 2020

Main GCSEs:

- Mathematics (passed)
- English (passed)

CAREER HISTORY

Havering Museum, London

July 2019 – July 2019

Volunteering Visitor Centre Assistant

- Giving tours of the Museum to individuals/groups
- Welcoming and explaining exhibits to visitors
- Assisting with club events within the museum
- Helping curators to set up, pack/unpack items
 Selling catalogues, books, souvenirs, etc.

Crowlands Primary School, London

May 2017 – May 2017

Volunteering Teaching Assistant

- Teaching English and Math to Nursery school pupils
- providing a safe and stimulating environment that facilitates learning
- organising and supervising play and work activities (for example reading, cooking, music, dancing etc)
- Maintaining records
- Monitoring and recording progress

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React.js
- jQuery
- Git
- GitHub
- Implementing APIs
- MS (Word, Excel & PowerPoint)
- Outlook

SKILLS, ACHIEVEMENTS AND INTERESTS

- 2019-2020: Deputy Head of House
- 2016-2019: Franklin Scholar at Frances Bardsley Academy for Girls
- 2018-2019: Franklin Scholar Mentor at FBA
- 2016-2017: Vice Form President at Frances Bardsley Academy for Girls
- 2012: Queens Theatre music Performance
- 2008: Piano Exam (Distinction)
- Interests include:
 - o Singing -St Edwards Choir member & FBA

- o Swimming
- o Netball player (2014-2018)
- o Piano player